pricelessarabia.com 2014-06-28

# MasterCard Priceless Arabia | Global Privacy Policy

**PRICELESS ARABIA - PRIVACY POLICY**

MasterCard respects your privacy.  This Privacy Policy describes how we process personal data, the types of personal data we collect, for what purposes we use that personal data, with whom we share it, and the choices you can make about our use of the personal data.  We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the personal data and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.

MasterCard International Incorporated (“ **MasterCard** ”) is the entity responsible for the processing of your personal data in the context of the Priceless Arabia Program (“ **Priceless Arabia** ”).  Your visit to [www.pricelessarabia.com](http://www.pricelessarabia.com/) (the “Site”) and participation in Priceless Arabia is subject to this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Use.  

This Privacy Policy applies to the personal data collected via Priceless Arabia only.  It does not cover the collection and use of your personal data on any MasterCard branded websites or by your MasterCard Card issuers (e.g., your bank), or any other information or communications that may reference to MasterCard outside the program (e.g., communications from banks, card issuers).  For more information about MasterCard’s privacy practices outside the scope of Priceless Arabia, please visit our Global Privacy Policy at [www.mastercard.com](http://www.mastercard.com/).

Children and minors (under the age of 18) are not eligible to register in Priceless Arabia.  

Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:

     1.  Personal Data We Collect and How We Use it  
    1.1 Personal Data You Provide Us Directly  
    1.2 Personal Data We Collect Automatically  
2.  Your Rights and Choices  
3.  Information We Share  
4.  Data Transfers  
5.  Links to Other Websites  
6.  Data Security  
7.  Update to this Privacy Policy  
8.  How to Contact Us

**_1.   Personal Data We Collect and How We Use it_**

We collect personal data in the context of Priceless Arabia.  By personal data we mean “any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person”. The personal data we process is either provided directly by you or collected automatically.  

**1.1  Personal Data You Provide to Us Directly**

The personal data you provide to us directly are processed and used only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  The personal data that you provide in the context of Priceless Arabia are never obligatory, unless marked otherwise for the purpose of providing you with our services.  If you choose not to give some data, this may affect the way you navigate on the Site or the services that we can offer you.  Please find below information on how you may provide this data, the types of data you may submit, and how we may use the data.

 _Registration Process_

:  You may register with Priceless Arabia through the Site.  In order to register with Priceless Arabia, you must provide us with some of your personal data such as your e-mail address, password, first and last name and country.  You will also need to provide us with the first 8 digits of your credit card to allow us to provide Priceless Arabia offers and experiences and to allow us to verify that you are a valid MasterCard cardholder. You may also provide your mobile number and city. In addition, to complete your registration, you must accept the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy applicable to Priceless Arabia.  

 _World Elite Access_

:  If you are a World Elite MasterCard cardholder, you will be allowed to unlock the World Elite offers and experiences.  To access these offers and experiences, you must provide us with the first 8 digits of your credit card during the registration process.  This will allow us to verify that you are a valid World Elite MasterCard cardholder by checking the bank ID information.  

 _Marketing Communications and Offers_

:  During the registration process, you may decide to tell us your preferences so that we can let you know when related offers, opportunities or private events become available. For example, you may establish criteria for the types of marketing communications and offers you wish to receive (i.e., Travel & Hotels, Dining, Shopping, Sports, Attractions, Entertainment).  

In order to send you these marketing communications, we use your personal data such as your name, e-mail address, and preferences.  You can, at any time and free of charge, choose not to receive any notifications by utilizing the unsubscribe functionality within the e-mail or SMS sent to you, or by e-mailing us using: [pricelessarabia@mastercard.com](mailto:pricelessarabia@mastercard.com). You can also use the “My Profile” section to opt-out from receiving marketing communications or to specify which, if any, marketing communications you would like to receive.

 _Your account_

: At any time after logging in you can access your account by clicking on "My Profile". Once you have successfully entered the My Profile page, you can view or change your personal details (e.g., name, email address, password) and manage your e-mail subscriptions. You may select which type of offers (i.e., Travel & Hotels, Dining, Shopping, Sports, Attractions, Entertainment) about town you are interested in receiving via the monthly newsletter and other e-mail communications. You may also select to deactivate your Priceless Arabia account by contacting us at [pricelessarabia@mastercard.com](mailto:pricelessarabia@mastercard.com) or, where available, selecting the option in the My Profile section.

 _Social media_

:    You may select to "like" an offer, via your Facebook account or to "tweet" an offer using Twitter.  Social media providers such as Facebook or Twitter are independent from MasterCard, and do not necessarily share the same policy as MasterCard with regard to the protection of privacy.  Please verify their privacy policies if you decide to use their services.  MasterCard cannot be held liable for any of these social websites' content, use or privacy practices.

 _  
Personalized Services and Recommendations_

: If you are a registered user, and you have opted in to receive communications, we may use your personal data to provide you with personalized services and recommendations.  For example, we may suggest products, specific Merchant Offers, or other special marketing activities that would be of particular interest to you.  

In order to provide you with personalized content and the most relevant offers, content or messages, we will gather the personal data that you have provided directly and the personal data that we have collected automatically in order to create a user profile. This profile is matched with a pre-established profile that helps us to learn more about consumer behaviors and preferences, allows us to optimize our offers, and to improve our relationship with you.  

At any time after your registration, in the “My Profile” section, you can update your personal interest choices.  If you no longer want to benefit from our personalized services, you may request that your account be deactivated.  Please note that if you deactivate your account, you will no longer have access to Priceless Arabia.

 _Customer call center_

: If you contact us through the Priceless Arabia customer call center, you may be required to provide personal information (such as name, email address, phone number, area or location and the offer which you are interested in) to allow us to contact you to resolve your enquiries and to allow us to assist you with enquiries and provide customer service. Your call to the call center may also be recorded for quality, monitoring and training purposes.

 _Other Features_

:  We offer users of Priceless Arabia various features for their information and enjoyment (e.g., sweepstakes, promotions, contests), which we may change from time to time.  We may ask you to submit certain personal data so we can provide you with these features.  For more information about how your data will be processed for these specific features, please refer to the relevant privacy policy, if any.

 _ **1\. 2.   Personal Data We Collect Automatically**_

We may collect certain information by automated means (e.g., cookies, log-file, web beacons) when you participate in Priceless Arabia.  The data collected automatically are processed in order to improve Priceless Arabia, perform data analyses to assess the use of Priceless Arabia and any interaction with other sites (e.g. social media sites), and to provide you with the best information and services.  The information we collect in this way tells us, for example, how many users visited our website and the pages accessed, whether you have visited us before or if you are a new visitor, and helps us to identify features in which you may have the greatest interest.  This information also allows us to make improvements and to enhance your experience.

 _Log files and IP addresses_

:  Log files are web server files (containing information such as the domain name or IP address, URL, the http response code, the website from where you visit us or the date and duration of your visit) that are automatically created when an Internet user visits a site.  An IP address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet.  When you visit the Site, we may collect the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet.  For example, when you request a page from the Site, our servers log your IP address.  In combination with other data, this information helps us to learn what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what types of offers our customers like to see.  In addition, log files help us to detect disruptions to telecommunication equipment and to detect abuse of our services.

 _  
Cookies, web beacons and tracking links_

:  To improve your experience, we may also use cookies, web beacons and tracking links in the context of Priceless Arabia.  

**2.  Your Rights and Choices**

You have the right to receive information about the data stored about you and to access your personal data by using the contact information provided in the “How to Contact Us” section below.  You may also request at any time that your personal data be rectified or deleted if it is incorrect, inaccurate or outdated.  Following any data request for access, rectification or deletion, we will accommodate your enquiry as required by applicable law.  At any time, you may object on reasonable grounds relating to your particular situation to the processing of your personal data by MasterCard, except when otherwise provided by the applicable law.    

At any time, you can access your account by clicking on "My Profile". Once you have successfully entered the preferences page, you can view or change your personal details and manage your e-mail subscriptions by modifying the type of offers you are interested in receiving via the monthly newsletter and other e-mail communications. You can also choose not to receive marketing e-mails from us by using the opt-out option provided in each electronic marketing communication or by using the contact details provided in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

You may elect not to have a unique cookie identification number assigned to your computer to avoid aggregation and analysis of data collected on Priceless Arabia. If you would like to opt-out, click [here](https://www.mastercard.com/us/personal/en/general/web-analytics-opt-out.html). Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all our website features.

If you decide you no longer want MasterCard to process your personal data, at your request we will deactivate your account, and your data will be deleted except where otherwise provided by the applicable law.  You may request to deactivate your Priceless Arabia account by contacting us at [pricelessarabia@mastercard.com](mailto:pricelessarabia@mastercard.com) or, where available, selecting the option in the My Profile section. Please note that if you deactivate your account, you will no longer have access to Priceless Arabia.  

If we fall short of your expectations in processing your personal data, please tell us because it gives us an opportunity to fix the problem. You may contact us by using the contact details provided in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

**3.  Information We Share**

We do not disclose personal data collected in the context of Priceless Arabia, except as described here.  

We may share your personal data with our affiliates. We may also share your personal data provided with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf and in relation to the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  Examples include our operating platform provider, platform hosting, email service provider, fulfillment service provider and customer service or call centre providers. When we use third party service providers, we take all necessary steps to ensure a high level of data protection.  We require them to only process the data in accordance with our instructions and to guarantee the security of the data.  These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information, except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.

We have engaged The Entertainer FZ LLC to source for offers and experiences. When you select an offer and experience, you may be brought to The Entertainer FZ LLC’s website to redeem the offer and experience. The Entertainer FZ LLC will be processing personal data for its own purposes under the terms of the agreement MasterCard has with The Entertainer FZ LLC in the context of Priceless Arabia, and we invite you to read [The Entertainer’s Privacy Notice](http://www.theentertainerme.com/privacy-and-cookies) for more information on its privacy practices. In addition, other merchants may provide offers and experiences to you directly, and any collection or use of personal data by those merchants will be subject to those merchants’ privacy notice.

If you have an enquiry or complaint in relation to a particular offer or experience, we may route your enquiry or complaint (and hence personal data contained in the enquiry or complaint e.g., name, email address, phone number, the subject of your complaint) to the relevant merchant or The Entertainer FZ LLC (where The Entertainer FZ LLC had sourced for the offer or experience) in order for them to respond to the enquiry or complaint.

If you are using the mapping tool within Priceless Arabia, that service is provided by Google. Their collection and use of any data through your interaction with their mapping tool is governed by Google’s privacy policy and terms of use, which we suggest you read.

In addition, we may disclose personal data about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or pursuant to legal process, (ii) in response to a request from a court, law enforcement authorities or government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual criminal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any data we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets.  Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will endeavor to use reasonable efforts to seek that the transferee uses the personal data you have provided through Priceless Arabia in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**4.  Data Transfers**

The transfer of personal data outside of your country may be subject to restrictions.  If we transfer personal data outside of your country, we take all the necessary steps to ensure compliance with applicable data protection law, in particular, the legal requirements on adequate protection for data transfers to countries outside of your country.  

In the context of this program, MasterCard may transfer, process and store your personal data in a centralized database located at MasterCard International Inc - MasterCard’s headquarters located in the U. S., and in a database in Singapore.  MasterCard International Inc is certified under the EU-U.S. Safe Harbor privacy framework as set forth by the U. S.  Department of Commerce, and the European Commission to provide adequate protection to your personal data.  Please visit [www.MasterCard.com](http://www.mastercard.com/) or [click here](http://www.mastercard.com/us/personal/en/general/safe-harbor-privacy-policy.html) to view our Safe Harbor Privacy Policy.

**5.  Links to Other Websites**

On the Site, we provide links to other websites for your convenience.  In particular, Priceless Arabia offers you the possibility to share, link to or mention on social media outlets, such as Facebook or Twitter, anything you may find of interest.   These sites operate independently from Priceless Arabia and are not under our control.  These sites may have their own privacy policies in place, which we strongly suggest you review when you visit them.  We are not responsible for the content of these sites, any products or services that may be offered through these sites, the data processing activities that are conducted via those sites, or any other use of these sites.

**6.  Data Security**

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the personal data in our possession.  

When you provide personal data online, we use the industry standard for encryption on the Internet  – Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology – to help protect the information that you provide.  This Internet encryption standard scrambles data as it travels from your device to our server.  You will know that you are in a secure area of the Site when a lock icon appears on your screen that the “http” prefix of our URL address changes to “https. ”  The “s” represents “secure”.  We also use digital certificates to ensure that you are connected to the authentic Site.

Please note however that no collection or data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any data transmission.

We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (including unsolicited correspondence, such as letters, phone calls or e-mail messages).  If you believe your user name and password have been compromised, please contact us by following the instructions provided in the section "How to Contact Us" below.

**7.  Update to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post a prominent notice on our websites to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Policy and indicate at the top of the policy when it was most recently updated.
